

ABOUT

Date of Birth: February 27, 2001

Age: 20

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Location: Kwara State, Nigeria. Tel: +234 816 5602 856 Email: Shittut88@gmail.com

INTERESTS

Problem Solving

Books

Polishing Skillset

Mind Games

Physical Activities

Technologies

HOBBIES

Traveling
Gymming
Photography

SHITTU TUNDE

WEBSITE/GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a competent graphic/website designer with 4+ years of solid work experience designing sites and graphic content for agency clients. I am a creative person who is able to produce websites from concept to launch. Having a detailed understanding of best web designing principles and SEO best practice, my sites are optimised to load fast, be responsive and be a pleasure to use. I have worked effectively both independently and as part of a team, and I am capable of being highly productive either way.

QUALIFICATIONS

2021 NATIONAL DIPLOMA

Degree In Computer Technology Federal Polytechnic, Offa.

2018 Marketing Exper

Course.

2015

Guru Design Institute.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Excellence in Graphic Design

2019 FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Certification in Professional Web Design RisingStar Technologies.

2018 Marketing Expert
Excellence in PPC
Rana Institute

2018 SSCE

Secondary School Certificate Mustapha Standard College.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

2018 TO PRESENT | FIVERR

Freelance Website and Graphic Designer for various business and developing organizations. I create and develop website layouts, projects, business identity designs and other corporate brand designs.

Web Developer

2020 TO PRESENT | JWS CONSULT

Professional Website Developer for JWS Consult and other organizations. I create and develop website portfolios, Educational Platforms, Charity sites, Media Kits as a Junior Team Leader.

Computer Operator

2014 - 2018 | RANA COMPUTERS & PRINTS

Proficient Computer Operator at Rana Computers, a Senior Operator at Online Research, Data Entry, MS Word, Presentations, Excel, Coreldraw Expert, Mini Video Edit, Project Consultant, Typing and Research.

EXPERTISE

SKILLS

GOOD COMMUNICATION
TIME MANAGEMENT

DIGITAL MARKETING ADAPTIVE LEARNING

CREATIVE SOLUTION

CLIENT MANAGEMENT

TEAMWORK & RESEARCH